Kettle and Idol
Now that we have finished eating ramen, let's have some sake, which brings us to the third use of the kettle: alcohol.
Yes, the third one is sake.
How do you like it?
I like this one.
I sometimes do insta-lives while drinking,
The first time was when I turned 20 years old with my managers,
I started out with my managers and I was turning 20 years old, and we thought it would be a good idea to have a drink at the live insta-live,
It turned out to be a great idea, like an idol drinking alcohol and doing an insta-live,
People were quite interested in it.
It's such a rarity.
That's unusual.
We've done it many times since then.
I like to drink.
Do you drink beer, wine or sake? Do you have a favorite?
My favorite is sake,
But I drink shochu most often.
Be a little careful.
If I drink too much sake, I get rice.
But I am careful about it, and I drink shochu.
Do you drink shochu almost every day? But I really can't resist my age,
The more I drink, the more it sticks to my body.
It's on my body.
Ah, yes, yes.Uh, yes, yes.
I refrained a little. Much.
Much?
Yes, a lot.
Something like 2 or 3 times a week.
Is it much stronger?
Not at all.
Not very strong at all,
But I drink it to the extent that it is weak,
I say "safe.
I'm doing okay now,
I'm doing fine.
No accidents.
So far.
I heard that you were drinking and suddenly started crying during a live broadcast,
Is that rumored to be the case?
Yes.
No. Yes, there was.
There is, isn't there?
Yes, there is. That couldn't be helped.
When Reni-chan announced her marriage,
That couldn't be helped.
It was just...,
I really screamed at home.
When the announcement was made, I was so upset.When there was a crazy announcement.
And I was so happy at night that I cried while drinking at the live delivery.
I ate cake and cried while drinking.
LOL.
And now, well, I don't know if I'm still among your fans.
I thought I had tears in me.
Hee! Really?
I didn't think it was in there. I thought I didn't have tears. Really? I didn't think it was early.
Tears? I didn't think so.
I remember you crying a lot behind our backs at the Stuffula festival.
I cry a lot.
Only every once in a while?
No, I really feel like a parent.
You said you cried more than the other winners.
That's right.
I cry before they even feel it.
It's the same every time, isn't it? That's right. They cry before they realize it.
That's true every time, isn't it?
Yes, the second time or so, I was embarrassed,
The second time or so, I was so embarrassed that I thought I shouldn't turn my face forward and cry,
I was so embarrassed the second time I cried that I thought I shouldn't turn my face forward, but I didn't feel that there were any tears.
But I felt that my tears connected with the Wada family,
That's right. There is drama in Atapura.
Atapura has drama. There is drama. Are there any new button genres that are being added recently?
I heard that when you started working on this one, this one became more tasty,I heard that when I started to try this one, this one started to taste better,
Or that you didn't like beer in the past, but now you can enjoy it at all, all the way from the beginning?
But it is true that I was surprised when I drank beer for the first time.
But after two or three times, when I am tired, I feel like, "Oh, I want to drink beer,
I feel like having a beer.
When I'm sweating after a lesson or something,
When I change into my clothes, I feel like having a beer.
Nighttime and idols
Hmmm...
Hang in there, Hajimasan.
Hajimasan go for it!
This show is
Ms. Shaw
Norika-san
Toshikazu
Satomi-san
Iru-Run provided this program.
Thank you very much!
See you soon!
We sent it to you.
Thank you very much. See you soon.